Greater Hartford Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1983.0004
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Greater Hartford Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records
undated, 1947-1982
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1983.0004
17 Linear Feet
The Greater Hartford Labor Council (GHLC) was formed in 1957. All local unions belonging to an international affiliated to the AFL-CIO or affiliated to the AFL-CIO directly are able to join the central labor body in their region upon payment of dues.
History
The Greater Hartford Labor Council (GHLC) was formed in 1957. The Hartford Central Labor Union (circa 1890s-October 1957) was the predecessor. The Greater Hartford Industrial Union Council (circa 1938-1957) was the CIO predecessor. The first regular monthly meeting of the GHLC was held on 2 October 1957. Peter J. Rossano served as the first president of the Council.
All local unions belonging to an international affiliated to the AFL-CIO or affiliated to the AFL-CIO directly are able to join the central labor body in their region upon payment of dues.
Scope and Content
The collection includes official minutes, correspondence, legal and financial documents, publications, photographs and related ephemera pertaining to the Greater Hartford Labor Council and its predecessor organizations. The minutes for the GHLC are incomplete although the years 1968 through 1978 are more comprehensively documented. Within the files of the President and Recording Secretary of the GHLC are materials pertaining to community service and public education.
Of particular interest is the relationship of the GHIUC-CIO with the State Council and the allegations of communist sympathies within the labor movement.
Arrangement
Series I: Hartford Central Labor Union—AFL (1949-1957). Contains financial records, including one ledger book of receipts and disbursements for 1955-1957.
Series II: Greater Hartford Industrial Union—CIO (undated, 1947-1957)is arranged into four subseries: Constitutions and Minutes, Correspondence and Subject Files, Financial Records, Connecticut State Industrial Union Council—CIO. Contains a copy of the GHIUC constitution and official minutes of meetings, incoming and outgoing correspondence, memoranda, reports, publications, auditor's and other financial reports.
Series III: Administrative Policy and Finance (undated, 1956-1981) Arranged into four subseries: By-Laws and Constitutions, Committee On Political Education (COPE), Newsclippings and Financial Records. Contains administrative records of the GHLC, minutes, financial records and clippings pertaining to labor activity in Connecticut.
Series IV: Minutes (undated, 1957-1982) pertain to monthly Executive Board and Delegate meetings and includes agendas, roll sheet, associated correspondence, committee reports, financial reports, official officer election materials, dues and membership lists, strike and boycott information, information about donations of funds and services, materials about state and municipal political endorsements and printed materials.
Series V: General Administration (undated, 1957-1982) consist of the files of the President and Recording Secretary of the GHLC. Includes correspondence (AFL-CIO International and local affiliates), delegates credential forms, resolutions, financial materials, requests for moral and monetary support for boycotts and strikes, information about state and local political candidates prepared by the Committee on Political Education (COPE), flyers and brochures for labor educational opportunities, requests and thank yous letters for charity donations, and social event correspondence. Community service files include material from the Community Renewal Team, the Greater Hartford Process, and the Human Resources Development Institute.
Series VI: Connecticut State Labor Council (undated, 1957-1982) has two subseries: Minutes and Correspondence and Subject Files. Consists of records received by the GHLC as an affiliate of the CSLC including: correspondence, reports, press releases, convention and financial materials.
Series VII: Printed Materials, Photographs and Memorabilia (undated, circa 1950-1978) is divided into three subseries: Printed Materials, Photographs and Memorabilia. The series includes newsletters and educational materials, photographs, membership cards, ribbons, audiotapes, and posters.
Series VIII: Royal Industrial Union (undated, 1946-1977) was collected by William E. Kuehnel, Chairman of the Retired Workers Chapter, Royal Industrial Union, Local 937, the series contains constitution, by-laws, correspondence, financial records, and newsletters.
Series IX: Greater Hartford Building and Construction Trades Council (undated, 1975-1982) contains records collected by William E. Kuehnel as Acting Secretary of the GHBCTC and includes minutes, correspondence, subject files, newsclippings and press releases.
The last two series are not part of Kuehnel's files as Recording Secretary of the GHLC but provide information of related interest to the activities of the GHLC.
Acquisition Information
The materials were deposited in the Connecticut Labor Archives (now part of Archives & Special Collections, Thomas J. Dodd Research Center) on 26 July 1983, through action of the delegate meeting of the GHLC.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Automobile industry workers; Labor unions; Resolutions (administrative records); Political participation; United States (nation); Connecticut (state); Press releases; Labor policy; Labor leaders; bylaws (administrative records); Financial Records; Publications (documents); Hartford (inhabited place); Administrative records; Collective labor agreements; Industrial relations; Law; Education; Strikes and lockouts; Legislation; Labor; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Construction workers; Social service; Construction industry; Correspondence; Constitutions; Kuehnel, William E.; American Federation of Labor; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.)
- Series I: Hartford Central Labor Union—AFL, 1949-1957
  - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records, 1957 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Ledger Book, 1955-1957; (1 v.) (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Membership and Dues Book, 1949-1957; (1 v.) (Box 1:, Folder 4)
- Series II: Greater Hartford Industrial Union—CIO, undated, 1947-1957
  - Subseries A:Constitutions and Minutes, undated, 1948-1955
    - Constitution, undated (Box 2:, Folder 5)
    - Minute Book, 1948-1950 (Box 2:, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 2:, Folder 7)
    - Minutes (notes), 1949-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 8)
    - Roll Call, undated, 1955 (Box 2:, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence and Subject Files, undated, 1948-1957
    - Board of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 2:, Folder 10)
    - Bulkley High School, 1950-1951 (Box 2:, Folder 11)
    - CIO, 1951-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 12-15)
    - Colt's Local 270, 1948-1954 (Box 2:, Folder 16)
    - COPE, 1956 (Box 2:, Folder 17)
    - Council Bulletin, undated (Box 2:, Folder 18)
    - Delegates credentials, 1950-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 19)
    - Defense Production Act, 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 20)
    - Grave Diggers Agreement, undated (Box 2:, Folder 21)
    - German Trade Unionists, 1949 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
    - Greater Hartford Community Council, 1951-1953 (Box 2:, Folder 23)
    - Greater Hartford Council for UNESCO, 1950-1951 (Box 2:, Folder 24)
    - Greater Hartford Council on Economic Education, 1952-1953 (Box 2:, Folder 25)
    - Hartford Rehabilitation Center, 1954 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - Membership Lists, 1950-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - IUE Local 260 arbitrations, 1957 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
    - NAACP Housing, undated (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - Resolution on Eisenhower, 1948 (Box 2:, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified materials, undated (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified materials, 1948-1957 (Box 2:, Folder 32-41)
  - Subseries C: Financial Records, 1948-1955
    - Auditor's reports, 1951-1954 (Box 2:, Folder 42)
    - Semi-Annual reports, 1949-1954 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
    - Bonds, 1948-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Subseries D: Connecticut State Industrial Union Council—CIO, 1947-1956
    - Minutes—Executive Board, 1948-1955 (Box 2:, Folder 45-51)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 2:, Folder 52-59)
    - Financial Reports, 1948-1952 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
- Series III: Administrative Policy and Finance, undated, 1956-1981
  - Subseries A: By-Laws and Constitutions, undated, 1959-1981
    - By-Laws, undated, 1960-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 61)
    - By-Law revision, 1959-1981 (Box 3:, Folder 62-63)
    - AFL-CIO Model Constitutions, 1965-1971 (Box 3:, Folder 64)
  - Subseries B: Committee On Political Education (COPE), undated, 1956-1976
    - By Laws, undated, 1959 (Box 3:, Folder 65)
    - Minutes, 1956-1965 (Box 3:, Folder 66)
    - Financial reports (quarterly), 1975-1976 (Box 3:, Folder 67)
  - Subseries C: Newsclippings, 1960s-1970s
    - GHLC Activities, 1960s-1970s (Box 3:, Folder 68)
    - Connecticut Labor Issues, 1960s-1970s (Box 3:, Folder 69)
  - Subseries D: Financial Records, 1957-1979
    - Auditor's reports (yearly), 1958-1976 (Box 3:, Folder 70)
    - Auditor's reports (quarterly), 1957-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 71)
    - Monthly reports, 1964-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1975-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
- Series IV: Minutes, undated, 1957-1982
  - Roll Calls, undated (Box 4:, Folder 74)
  - Executive Board and Delegates Meetings, 1957-1966 (Box 4:, Folder 75-84)
  - Executive Board and Delegates Meetings, 1967-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 85-159)
  - Executive Board and Delegates Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 6:, Folder 160-188)
  - Executive Board and Delegates Meetings, 1977-1982 (Box 7:, Folder 189-239)
- Series V: General Administration, undated, 1957-1982
  - Board, Committee, Delegates and Member lists, undated (Box 8:, Folder 240)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 8:, Folder 241)
  - Delegates credentials, undated (Box 8:, Folder 242)
  - Kuehnel, Bill—personal, undated (Box 8:, Folder 243)
  - Pledge of the GHLC, undated (Box 8:, Folder 244)
  - Political activities, undated (Box 8:, Folder 245)
  - Resolutions, undated (Box 8:, Folder 246)
  - Strike and boycott correspondence and flyers, undated (Box 8:, Folder 247)
  - General, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 248)
  - Community Services, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 249)
  - COPE, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 250)
  - Delegates credentials, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 251)
  - Recording Secretary Correspondence to Locals and Officials, 1957 (Box 8:, Folder 252)
  - General, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 253-256)
  - COPE, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 257)
  - Delegates credentials, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 258)
  - Income Tax Exemption material, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 259)
  - Recording Secretary Correspondence to Locals and Officials, 1958 (Box 8:, Folder 260)
  - General, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 261-262)
  - Connecticut Department of Public Welfare Study, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 263)
  - COPE, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 264-265)
  - Delegates credentials, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 266)
  - Income Tax Exemption material, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 267)
  - Recording Secretary Correspondence to Locals and Officials, 1959 (Box 8:, Folder 268)
  - General, 1960 (Box 8:, Folder 269-270)
  - Delegates credentials, 1960 (Box 8:, Folder 271)
  - Labor-Clergy Meeting, 1960 (Box 8:, Folder 272)
  - Recording Secretary Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8:, Folder 273)
  - General, 1961 (Box 8:, Folder 274)
  - Delegates credentials, 1961 (Box 8:, Folder 275)
  - Recording Secretary Correspondence to Locals and Officials, 1961 (Box 8:, Folder 276)
  - General, 1962 (Box 1:, Folder 277-278)
  - Community Services, 1962 (Box 9:, Folder 279)
  - COPE, 1962 (Box 9:, Folder 280-281)
  - Delegates credentials, 1962 (Box 9:, Folder 282)
  - General, 1963 (Box 9:, Folder 283)
  - Blutrade Program, 1963 (Box 9:, Folder 284)
  - Community Renewal Team of Hartford, 1963 (Box 9:, Folder 285)
  - Delegates credentials, 1963 (Box 9:, Folder 286)
  - General, 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 287)
  - AFL-CIO (National), 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 288-289)
  - Delegates credentials, 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 290)
  - Secretary's correspondence, 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 291)
  - Scholarship, 1964 (Box 9:, Folder 292)
  - General, 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 293-294)
  - AFL-CIO (National), 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 295)
  - Community Renewal Team of Greater Hartford, 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 296)
  - COPE, 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 297)
  - Delegates credentials, 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 298)
  - Regional Advisory Committee for the Capitol Region, 1965 (Box 9:, Folder 299)
  - General, 1966 (Box 9:, Folder 300)
  - Delegates credentials, 1966 (Box 9:, Folder 301)
  - Political endorsements, 1966 (Box 9:, Folder 302)
  - General, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 303-304)
  - Delegates credentials, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 305)
  - Strike flyers, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 306)
  - Strike: Sheraton Hotel, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 307)
  - General, 1968 (Box 9:, Folder 308-309)
  - COPE, 1968 (Box 9:, Folder 310)
  - COPE, 1968 (Box 10:, Folder 311-312)
  - Delegate credentials, 1968 (Box 10:, Folder 313)
  - General, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 314-315)
  - COPE, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 316)
  - Delegates credentials, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 317)
  - Kuehnel, Bill: retirement, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 318)
  - Strike: Local 644, 1969 (Box 10:, Folder 319)
  - General, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 320-321)
  - COPE: political questionnaire, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 322)
  - Delegates credentials, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 323)
  - Democratic State Platform, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 324)
  - Fauliso, Joseph, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 325)
  - Labor Issues—State, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 326)
  - Senior Citizens, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 327)
  - General, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 328)
  - Delegates credentials, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 329)
  - Political endorsements, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 330)
  - "Table Talk v. Teamsters", 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 331)
  - General, 1972 (Box 10:, Folder 332-333)
  - Delegates credentials, 1972 (Box 10:, Folder 334)
  - Union Prescription Plan, 1972 (Box 10:, Folder 335)
  - General, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 336-337)
  - Delegate credentials, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 338)
  - Political endorsements, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 339-340)
  - General, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 341-343)
  - CETA in Middlesex County, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 344)
  - Delegates credentials, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 345)
  - Political endorsements, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 346)
  - General, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 347-349)
  - Delegates credentials, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 350)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 351)
  - Political endorsements, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 352)
  - General, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 353-356)
  - CETA in Middlesex County, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 357)
  - Community Services, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 358)
  - COPE, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 359)
  - Delegates credentials, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 360)
  - HMO Feasibility Study, 1976 (Box 11:, Folder 361)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 362)
  - Political endorsements, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 363)
  - Strike: flyers, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 364)
  - Strike: firefighters, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 365)
  - Union Label Week, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 366)
  - United Way, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 367)
  - General, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 368-369)
  - Comprehensive Manpower Program: CETA, YCCIP, YETP, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 370)
  - COPE: election material, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 371)
  - Council on Employment and Taxation, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 372)
  - Delegate credentials, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 373)
  - GHLC Election, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 374)
  - Greater Hartford Process, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 375-376)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 377)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 378)
  - Strike: Charles Manufacturing Company and Mason-Tyler Manufacturing Company, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 379)
  - Union Prescription Center, 1977 (Box 12:, Folder 380)
  - General, 1978 (Box 12:, Folder 381-383)
  - AFL-CIO: Meany Correspondence, 1978 (Box 12:, Folder 384)
  - CETA Masterplan, 1978-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 385)
  - CETA Masterplan, 1978-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 386)
  - CETA and Public Service Employment, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 387-389)
  - Community Services Expeditor Program, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 390-392)
  - Comprehensive Community Management Planning Program, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 393)
  - Comprehensive Manpower Program, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 394)
  - COPE: Women's Activities Department, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 395)
  - Council on Employment and Fair Taxation, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 396)
  - Delegates credentials, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 397)
  - Greater Hartford Process, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 398-400)
  - Hartford Area Manpower Planning Council, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 401)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 402-403)
  - Metal Machine Concept for Youth, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 404)
  - Strike: Stevens, J. P., 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 405)
  - United Way, 1978 (Box 13:, Folder 406)
  - General, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 407)
  - Community Services, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 408)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 409)
  - Delegates credentials, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 410)
  - Dorsey, Mike: resignation, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 411)
  - Greater Hartford Process, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 412)
  - Hartford Area Manpower Planning Council, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 413)
  - HMO Feasibility Study, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 414)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 415)
  - President's outgoing correspondence, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 416)
  - Redcoach Lettuce Boycott, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 417)
  - Regional Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 418)
  - General, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 419)
  - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 420)
  - CETA, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 421)
  - Community Serices Committee, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 422-428)
  - Delegates credentials, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 429)
  - Humphrey, Muriel, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 430)
  - P. A. Testa Company, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 431)
  - General, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 432)
  - Delegate credentials (by local name), 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 433-486)
  - General, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 487)
- Series VI: Connecticut State Labor Council, undated, 1957-1982
  - Subseries A: Minutes, undated, 1958-1978
    - Executive Board, 1958-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 488-503)
    - Community Services Committee, 1961 (Box 15:, Folder 504)
    - Employment and Training Committee, 1978 (Box 15:, Folder 505)
    - Union Label Committee, 1961 (Box 15:, Folder 506)
  - Subseries B: Correspondence and Subject Files, undated, 1957-1982
    - COPE, 1960, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 507)
    - Employment Improvement Program, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 508)
    - Financial Reports and Statements, 1968-1976 (Box 15:, Folder 509)
    - G.E. Contributions, 1970 (Box 15:, Folder 510)
    - Income Tax Educational Conference, 1963 (Box 15:, Folder 511)
    - Officer Lists, undated, 1965-1975 (Box 15:, Folder 512)
    - Press Releases, undated, 1972 (Box 15:, Folder 513)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1978, 1982 (Box 15:, Folder 514-535)
    - Convention material, 1965-1977 (Box 15:, Folder 536-546)
- Series VII: Printed Materials, Photographs and Memorabilia, undated, circa 1950-1978
  - Subseries A: Printed Materials, undated, circa 1960-1978
    - AFL-CIO, undated (Box 16)
      - General, 1960s (Box 16:, Folder 547)
      - Education Department, undated, 1963 (Box 16:, Folder 548-550)
      - Hatch Act Information, undated (Box 16:, Folder 551)
      - Legislative Department, 1965-1972 (Box 16:, Folder 552-554)
      - "Labor Law Reform", 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 555)
      - Political Action material, undated (Box 16:, Folder 556)
    - American Federation of Teachers, undated (Box 16:, Folder 557)
    - Connecticut United Auto Workers, 1967 (Box 16:, Folder 558)
    - Democratic Leftist Newsletter, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 559)
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1966 (Box 16:, Folder 560)
    - United Auto Workers, undated, 1969 (Box 16:, Folder 561)
  - Subseries B: Photographs, undated, 1974-1978
    - Unidentified negatives, undated (Box 16:, Folder 562)
    - Unidentified images, undated, 1974-1976 (Box 16:, Folder 563)
    - Connecticut Trade Union Council, 1976 (Box 16:, Folder 564)
    - New Haven Central Labor Council Occupational Health Display, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 565)
    - Telethon, WHNB TV-30, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 566)
  - Subseries C: Memorabilia, undated, circa 1950-1970
    - Identification cards—GHLC, undated (Box 16:, Folder 567)
    - Conference ribbon, 1969 (Box 16:, Folder 568)
    - Meeting tapes, 1961-1962 (Box 16:, Folder 569)
    - Posters—Political and Labor issues, 1950s-1970s (Box 17:, Folder 570)
- Series VIII: Royal Industrial Union, undated, 1946-1977
  - Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 18:, Folder 571)
    - The 265 Association, 1946, 1972 (Box 18:, Folder 572)
    - UAW Local 937, 1965 (Box 18:, Folder 573)
    - UAW—Community Action Program, undated (Box 18:, Folder 574)
  - Community Action Program, undated, 1970-1972 (Box 18:, Folder 575)
  - Election material, Local 937, undated, 1966-1969 (Box 18:, Folder 576)
  - Employment comparison chart (see Posters, Box 17), undated (Box 18:, Folder 577)
  - Financial Records, 1967-1972 (Box 18:, Folder 578)
  - Resolutions, [1970?] (Box 18:, Folder 579)
  - Correspondence, undated, 1962-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 580-596)
  - Local 937 Reports (Newsletter), 1961-1971 (Box 18:, Folder 597)
  - Newsletters and Clippings, 1970s (Box 18:, Folder 598)
- Series IX: Greater Hartford Building and Construction Trades Council, undated, 1975-1982
  - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 599-600)
  - Agreements, 1976-1977 (Box 18:, Folder 601)
  - Housing Rehabilitation and Development, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 602)
  - Manpower and Training Program, undated (Box 18:, Folder 603)
  - Press Clippings and News Releases, ca. 1970s (Box 18:, Folder 604)
  - U.S. Department of Labor Employment Standards, 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 605)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files, undated, 1976-1978 (Box 18:, Folder 606-610)